Guide to the Stanford University Electronic Theses and Dissertations Signature Pages SC4-1509
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University electronic theses and dissertations signature pages
2009-2016
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University
SC4-1509
10.25 Linear Feet 23 boxes
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical/Historical note
The Stanford University Electronic Theses and Dissertations (ETD) program began in 2009. This collection contains the original signature pages for all ETDs submitted since the inception of this program.
Arrangement
Dissertation signature pages are arranged in chronological order by academic quarter.
Scope and Contents
The Stanford University Electronic Theses and Dissertations (ETD) program began in 2009. This collection contains the original signature pages for all ETDs submitted since the inception of this program, arranged by date.
Electronic dissertations; Stanford University -- Students.; Stanford University
- 2009 Fall-2010 Spring (K-L) (Box 1)
- 2010 Spring (Ma-Se)-2010 Summer/Fall (Box 2)
- 2011 Winter-2011 Spring M-Z (Box 3)
- 2011 Summer (Box 4)
- 2011 Fall-2012 Winter (Box 5)
- 2012 Spring (Box 6)
- 2012 Summer (Box 7)
- 2012 Fall (Box 11)
- 2013 Winter (Box 12)
- 2013 Spring (Box 8)
- 2013 Summer (Box 9)
- 2013 Fall (Box 10)
- 2014 Winter (Box 11)
- 2014 Spring (Box 13)
- 2014 Summer (Box 14)
- 2014 Fall (Box 15)
- 2015 Winter (Box 16)
- 2015 Spring (Box 17)
- 2015 Summer (Box 18)
- 2015 Fall (Box 19)
- 2016 Winter (Box 20)
- 2016 Spring (Box 21)
- 2016 Summer (Box 22)
- 2016 Fall (Box 23)